Sheet Music Collection
Sheet Music Collection
- Sheet music
  - Lesser-known composers
    - Furst, William Vocal Gems from The Comedy Opera Success The Isle of Champagne, as produced by the Thomas Q. Seabrooke Opera Co., written by Charles Alfred Byrne and Louis Harrison, vocal (songs) (Oversize 7)
    - Gabriel, Charles H. The "Glory Song", vocal (choral) (Oversize 7)
    - Gabriel, Charles H. The Lord Arose, vocal (duet) (soprano or tenor and alto) (Oversize 7)
    - Gabriel, Charles H. The Voice Divine, words by Horatio Bonar, vocal (duet) (soprano and tenor) (Oversize 7)
    - Gabriel, Virginia In the Gloaming, words by Meta Orred, vocal (song) (signed "J. L. Butler, BGF Seminary, Virginia") (Oversize 7)
    - Gade, N. W. The Water-Lily, vocal (choral) two copies (Oversize 7)
    - Galbraith, J. Lamont The Shadow of the Ev'ning Hour, words by Adelaide Proctor, vocal (choral with keyboard accompaniment) two copies (Oversize 7)
    - Gale, Walter C. As pants the hart, vocal (duet with piano or organ accompaniment) (soprano and contralto) (Oversize 7)
    - Gardana, Enea Capriccio sull'Opera Lindadi Chamounix variato per Chitarra dedicato al suo Allievo Signor Luigi Petiti (Op. 3), guitar (solo) (signed by W. P. Graham) (Oversize 7)
    - Gardana, Enea Melodie nell'Opera Un Ballo in Maschera di Verdi, transcrite per chitarra, guitar (solo) (signed by W. P. Graham) (Oversize 7)
    - Gaul, Alfred R. The Singers, edited by Charles Belcarris, vocal (choral with keyboard accompaniment for rehearsal only) two copies, one marked "piano" (Oversize 7)
    - Gaul, Alfred R. List! The Cherubic Host (from The Holy City), vocal (choral with piano accompaniment) (women's voices with bass and soprano solos) (Oversize 7)
    - Gaynor, Jessie L. Cuddle Doon, words by Alice C. D. Riley, vocal (song) (mezzo-soprano) (Oversize 7)
    - Geehl, Henry E. For You Above, words by P. J. O'Reilly, vocal (song with piano and violin accompaniment) (Oversize 7)
    - Geibel, Adam Lullaby, words from "The Mistress of the Manse" by Holland, vocal (song) (mezzo-soprano) (signed "Jennie Lee Butler" "BGFS") (Oversize 7)
    - Geibel, Adam The Messenger March, arr. by A. Luck (orchestrated sheet music) (Oversize 7)
    - Genée, Richard Italian Salad, arranged by Perry Jackman, edited by N. Clifford Page vocal (tenor or soprano solo and chorus with piano accompaniment) two copies (Oversize 7)
    - Genée, Richard Potpourri aus Nisida, (orchestral sheet music) (Oversize 7)
    - Gibson, Sidney Just as the Ship Went Down: a song of the sea, words by Edith Maida Lessing, music also by Bernie Adler, vocal (song) (Oversize 7)
    - Gilbert, L. Wolfe Are You from Heaven?, also by Anatol Friedland, vocal (song with piano accompaniment) (Oversize 7)
    - Giuliani, Mauro La caccia Oran Rondo per lira o chitarra sola, guitar or lyre (solo) (Oversize 7)
    - Giuliani, Mauro Sei Arie Nazionali Scozzesi variate per la Chitarra o Lira, dedicate a madamigella Elisabetta Mackenzie, guitar or lyre (solo) (signed by W. P. Graham) (Oversize 7)
    - Glenn, Edwin Atlee Berwick High School Alma Mater, includes Berwick High School Battle Song, vocal (choral with keyboard accompaniment) (Oversize 7)
    - Glover, Stephen Our Beautiful Mountain Home, words by J. F. Carpenter, vocal (duet with keyboard accompaniment) (signed "From Lucie I. Pendleton to Phillie") (Oversize 7)
    - Glover, Stephen Prince Albert's Grand March, or, Gov. Porter's March, as performed by the Military Bands, piano (solo) (signed "Phillie A. Stover" "Willow Grove, Shenandoah County, Va.") (Oversize 7)
    - Goble, W. A. The Yankee Princess, keyboard (solo) (Oversize 7)
    - Godard, Benjamin Lullaby from Jocelyn / Cachés dans cet asile, English version by Nathan Haskell Dole, vocal (song with piano accompaniment) (mezzo-soprano or baritone) (Oversize 7)
    - Godard, Benjamin En plain air: Suite de cinq morceaux pour violon avec accompagnement d'orchestre ou de piano par Benjamin Godard (Op. 145): No. 1: A l'ombre, violin (solo with piano accompaniment) (Oversize 7)
    - Godard, Benjamin En plain air: Suite de cinq morceaux pour violon avec accompagnement d'orchestre ou de piano par Benjamin Godard (Op. 145): No. 2: Sous la charmille, violin (solo with piano accompaniment) (Oversize 7)
    - Godard, Benjamin En plain air: Suite de cinq morceaux pour violon avec accompagnement d'orchestre ou de piano par Benjamin Godard (Op. 145): No. 3: En regardant le ciel, violin (solo with piano accompaniment) (Oversize 7)
    - Godard, Benjamin En plain air: Suite de cinq morceaux pour violon avec accompagnement d'orchestre ou de piano par Benjamin Godard (Op. 145): No. 4: Danse rustique, violin (solo with piano accompaniment) (Oversize 7)
    - Godard, Benjamin En plain air: Suite de cinq morceaux pour violon avec accompagnement d'orchestre ou de piano par Benjamin Godard (Op. 145): No. 5: La fée du hallier, violin (solo with piano accompaniment) (Oversize 7)
    - Godard, Benjamin Scènes Ecossaises pour violon avec accompagnement d'orchestre ou de piano par Benjamin Godard (Op. 138): No 1: Légende Pastorale, violin (solo with piano accompaniment) (Oversize 7)
    - Godard, Benjamin Scènes Ecossaises pour hautbois ou violon avec accompagnement d'orchestre ou de piano par Benjamin Godard (Op. 138): No 2: Sérénade à Mabel: Edition pour violon, violin (solo with piano accompaniment) (Oversize 7)
    - Godard, Benjamin Scènes Ecossaises pour violon avec accompagnement d'orchestre ou de piano par Benjamin Godard (Op. 138): No 3: Marche des Highlanders, violin (solo with piano accompaniment) (Oversize 7)
    - Godard, Benjamin Six morceaux pour violon avec accompagnement de piano, Op. 128: No. 1: Rêverie, violin (solo with piano accompaniment) (Oversize 7)
    - Godard, Benjamin Six morceaux pour violon avec accompagnement de piano, Op. 128: No. 2: Gavotte, violin (solo with piano accompaniment) (Oversize 7)
    - Godard, Benjamin Six morceaux pour violon avec accompagnement de piano, Op. 128: No. 3: Adagio pathétique, violin (solo with piano accompaniment) (Oversize 7)
    - Godard, Benjamin Six morceaux pour violon avec accompagnement de piano, Op. 128: No. 4: Mazurk sentimentale, violin (solo with piano accompaniment) (Oversize 7)
    - Godard, Benjamin Six morceaux pour violon avec accompagnement de piano, Op. 128: No. 6: Staccato-Valse, violin (solo with piano accompaniment) (Oversize 7)
    - Goetzl, Anselm When the Cherry Blossoms Fall (Love is Love) from The Royal Vagabond, lyrics by William Cary Duncan, vocal (song) (signed by Frank C. Love) (Oversize 7)
    - Goldmark, Rubin Trio für pianoforte, violin und violoncello (Op. 1), piano trio (piano, violin, cello) (Oversize 7)
    - Götze, Carl Still wie die Nacht / Calm as the night, English version by Nathan Haskell Dole, vocal (duet with piano accompaniment) (baritone and soprano) two copies (Oversize 7)
    - Goublier, G. A Song of Praise, arr. by F. H. Brackett, freely translated from the French of S. and F. Borel by Nicholas Douty, vocal (duet) (soprano & baritone) (Oversize 7)
    - Graben-Hoffmann, Gustav Floating Onward, translated by M. J. Barnett, vocal (duet with piano accompaniment) (soprano and alto or baritone) (Oversize 7)
    - Granichstaedten, Bruno Zuschau'n kann ich nicht: Wiener Walzerlied aus Erik Charells "Im weissen Rössl", Text von Robert Gilbert, vocal (song with piano accompaniment) (Oversize 7)
    - Grey, Frank H. Two Concert Songs with Piano Accompaniment: No. 1: Bird-Man on High, Poem by Harriet Gaylord, vocal (song with piano accompaniment) (high voice) (Oversize 7)
    - Grimm, N. C. Rigoletto: opera di G. Verdi: "Caro nome che il mio cor", pezzi ridotti per chitarra sola, guitar (solo) (signed by W. P. Graham) (Oversize 7)
    - Gumbert, F. My Heart is Thine / Mein Herz das ist., English words by C. Linley, vocal (song) (Oversize 7)
    - Hadley, Henry A Ballade of June Roses, vocal (duet with keyboard accompaniment) (soprano and alto) (Oversize 7)
    - Hahn, Carl The Green Cathedral, verse by Gordon Johnstone, vocal (song) (high voice) (signed by Winifred S. Myers) (Oversize 7)
    - Hahn, Carl The Little Road Through Nazareth, verse by Gordon Johnstone, vocal (song with piano accompaniment) (high voice) (Oversize 7)
    - Hahn, Carl A Sign at Twilight, verse by Mary Leefe Laurence, vocal (song) (high voice) (Oversize 7)
    - Hall, J. Lincoln The Star of His Love Shines On, words by Francis McKinnon Morton, vocal (song) (medium voice) two copies (Oversize 7)
    - Hardway, F. Drum Waltz, dedicated to the Ladies of Cincinnati, piano (solo) (written: "Love of Millie & Joe" "Milly – Sept. 1886 (no. 16)") (Oversize 7)
    - Harker, F. Flaxington Blest Are the Pure in Heart, text by Rev. John Keble, vocal (song) (high voice) (Oversize 7)
    - Harker, F. Flaxington Four Songs for a Medium Voice with Piano Accompaniment (Op. 45): No. 2: Sing a song, sing a song in the morning, words by Grace Hibbard, vocal (song with piano accompaniment) (medium voice) (Oversize 7)
    - Harker, F. Flaxington Three Sacred Songs with Piano Accompaniment: No. 2: God shall wipe away all tears (Op. 49), vocal (song with piano accompaniment) (high voice) (Oversize 7)
    - Harker, F. Flaxington Two Sacred Songs with Piano Accompaniment: O Love That Wilt not Let Me Go, words by the Rev. George Matheson, vocal (song with piano accompaniment) (high voice) (Oversize 7)
    - Harrison, Charles (The Last Waltz with You Was) The Sweetest Waltz of All, words & music also by Fred Rose, vocal (song) (with optional ukulele accompaniment) (Oversize 7)
    - Hart, Maude Anita Beyond the Shining Gates of Gold (Op. 60), vocal (duet) (tenor or soprano and alto) two copies (Oversize 7)
    - Hartmann, J. P. E. 6 Karakterstykker / 6 Characterstücke / 6 Characteristic Pieces (Op. 50), new edition by Adolf Ruthart, piano (solos) (Oversize 7)
    - Hatton, George F. When Red Leaves Fall, words by Rosa Villiers, vocal (song) (Oversize 7)
    - Hatton, John Good-by, Sweetheart, Good-by, vocal (song) (Oversize 7)
    - Hatton, J. L. He That Hath a Pleasant Face, words by W. H. Bellamy, vocal (choral with piano accompaniment) two copies (Oversize 7)
    - Hauser, M. Lieder ohne Worte (Op. 11), violin (solos) (Oversize 7)
    - Hawley, C. B. Christ has opened Paradise, vocal (song) (high voice) two copies, one signed "Winifred S. Myers – Radnor" "Invictus – Bruno Huln" (Oversize 7)
    - Hawley, C. B. Just as I am, words by Charlotte Elliott, vocal (song) (high voice) two copies (Oversize 7)
    - Hawley, C. B. The King of love my shepherd is, words by Henry W. Baker, vocal (duet) (Oversize 7)
    - Hawley, C. B. The song that my heart's a-singing, words by Frank Chaffee, vocal (song) (soprano or tenor) (Oversize 7)
    - Hawley, C. B. Spring's Awakening, vocal (song with piano accompaniment) (soprano or tenor) (Oversize 7)
    - Hayden, W. L. Monastery Bells (Op. 150), guitar (solo) (Oversize 7)
    - Hays, Will S. The Little Old Cabin in the Lane, vocal (song and chorus) (Oversize 7)
    - Hays, Will S. Mollie Darling, vocal (song and chorus) (signed "To Jennie Lee – from Mrs. Duke") (Oversize 7)
    - Heartz, H. L. (Overall title unknown, first piece is Opening Ensemble: Oh, Shrine of Psyche!), piano (solos) (Oversize 8)
    - Henneberg, Paul Floretta: Cuban Caprice, (orchestral sheet music) (Oversize 8)
    - Henry, S. R. Oriental Musical Novelty: Pahjamah, also by D. Onivas (orchestral sheet music) (Oversize 8)
    - Herold, F. Ouverture zur Oper Zampa, piano trio (piano, violin, and cello) (Oversize 8)
    - Hewitt, J. H. Master and Pupil, vocal (duet with piano accompaniment) (soprano and baritone) (Oversize 8)
    - Higgs, H. M Vilia: from The Merry Widow, words by Adrian Ross, original music by Franz Lehár, vocal (song with piano accompaniment) (signed "Jean Aldrich Conrad") (Oversize 8)
    - Hinton, Arthur I Dare Not, words by Robert Herrick, vocal (choral) (keyboard accompaniment for practice only) (Oversize 8)
    - Hoffman, George Home Schottisch: Introducing the beautiful Melody old folks at home, piano (solo) (signed "Milly – Sept 24th 1886 (No. 17)" "Gussie Stilt from Sister Phe") (Oversize 8)
    - Hofmann, Richard Adelaide, composed by L. van Beethoven, arranged for solo violin and piano (Oversize 8)
    - Hogben, Ed Doozie, arr. by Louis Tocaben, piano (solo) (marked "Compliments of Publisher") (Oversize 8)
    - Holland, Justin Silvery Waves, original music by A. P. Wyman, arranged for the guitar, guitar (solo) (Oversize 8)
    - Holzmann, Abe Blaze-Away!, (orchestral sheet music) (Oversize 8)
    - Holzmann, Abe The Whip, arr. by J. Bodewalt Lampe (orchestral sheet music) (Oversize 8)
    - Howard, Great Somewhere in France is Daddy, vocal (song with piano accompaniment) (Oversize 8)
    - Howell, Charles T. By the Waters of Babylon, vocal (song) (high voice) (Oversize 8)
    - Hubbell, Raymond Melody Land, lyric by John L. Golden, vocal (song with piano accompaniment) (signed by Winifred S. Myers) (Oversize 8)
    - Hubbell, Raymond Poor Butterfly, words by John L. Golden, vocal (song with piano accompaniment) (signed by Winifred S. Myers) (Oversize 8)
    - Huerter, Charles Just as I am, words by Charlotte Elliott, vocal (song) two copies (Oversize 8)
    - Huerter, Charles O, Little Mate O'Mine, words by Francis J. Saunders, vocal (song) (high voice) (Oversize 8)
    - Huhn, Bruno Invictus, words by William Ernest Henley, vocal (song) (alto or bass) (Oversize 8)
    - Huhn, Bruno Sun of my soul, words by John Keble, vocal (song with piano or organ accompaniment) (high voice) (Oversize 8)
    - Hunter, J. Joys That We've Tasted with Variations for the Pianoforte, piano (solo) (signed "Phillie A. Stover" "Willow Grove" "Shenandoah County" "Va") (Oversize 8)
    - Ingraham, George The Owl and the Pussy Cat, vocal (choral with keyboard accompaniment) two copies (Oversize 8)
    - Itzel, Adam Jr. Lullaby from "The Tar and the Tartar", words by Harry B. Smith, vocal (song) (Oversize 8)
    - Jacobs, Walter Flower Waltz (Op. 39), banjo (solo or duet) (signed by H. Leslie Conrad) (Oversize 8)
    - Jaffe, Moe Collegiate, words and music also by Nat Bonx, vocal (song) (with optional ukulele accompaniment) (Oversize 8)
    - Jakobowski, E. Vocal Gems from Erminie, libretto by Claxson Bellamy and Harry Paulton, vocal (songs with piano accompaniment), Casino New York City (Oversize 8)
    - Jakobowski, E. Vocal Gems from Erminie, libretto by Claxson Bellamy and Harry Paulton, vocal (songs with piano accompaniment), published by Richard A. Saalfield (Oversize 8)
    - Jansa, I. Six duos progressives pour deux violins (Op. 46), violin (duets) (Oversize 8)
    - Jennings, J. H. Sounds from the Cottonfield, banjo (solo or duet with banjeaurine) (Oversize 8)
    - Jensen, Adolf Abendmusik für Pianoforte zu vier Händen (Op. 59), piano (four hands) (Oversize 8)
    - Jensen, Adolf Hochzeitsmusik (Festzug, Brautgesang, Reigen und Notturno) für Pianoforte zu vier Händen (Op. 45), piano (four hands) (signed "T. M. Osborne") (Oversize 8)
    - Jensen, Adolf Hochzeitsmusik für Violine und Pianoforte Heft 1: Festzug, Brautgesang (Op. 45), arranged by Reinhold Becker, violin (solo with piano accompaniment) (Oversize 8)
    - Jensen, Adolf Hochzeitsmusik für Violine und Pianoforte Heft 2: Reigen, Notturno (Op. 45), arranged by Reinhold Becker, violin (solo with piano accompaniment) (Oversize 8)
    - Jeremiah, David R. Open the Windows of Heaven, text by T. Jeremiah, vocal (song) two copies (Oversize 8)
    - Jerome, Frederic Sun of My Soul, words by John Keble, vocal (duet) (soprano and alto) (Oversize 8)
    - Jerome, Frederick Light at Evening Time, vocal (duet) (soprano or tenor and alto) (Oversize 8)
    - Jones, James Edmund Our Duty, words by Frederick George Scott, vocal (choral) (Oversize 8)
    - Jordan, Julian Rejoice and Sing, vocal (song with piano accompaniment) (alto or baritone) two copies (Oversize 8)
    - Jullien The Prima Donna Waltzes, piano (solos) (signed "Miss Gussie Stitt" "From G. E. D.") (Oversize 8)
    - Jungmann, Albert Du liegst mir im Herzen (Op. 344), (orchestral sheet music) (Oversize 8)
    - Kálmán, Emmerich Ha-za-zaa from Henry W. Savage's new Operette Sári (Der Zigeunerprimas), lyric by C. C. S. Cushing & E. P. Heath, vocal (song) (Oversize 8)
    - Kalmar Rebecca (Came Back from Mecca), also by Ruby, arranged by Arthur Lange (orchestral sheet music) (Oversize 8)
    - Kéler-Béla Lustspiel Overture (Op. 73), arr. by Theo. Moses (orchestral sheet music) (Oversize 8)
    - Kenneth, W. D. Watch Hill, banjo (solo or duet with guitar accompaniment) (Oversize 8)
    - Kerker, Gustave Vocal Gems from Rice's Fantastic Comic Opera Venus, libretto by C. A. Byrne and Louis Harrison, vocal (songs) (souvenir of the 100th performance at the Park Theatre, Monday Evening, Dec. 18, 1893) (Oversize 8)
    - Ketterer, Eugene L'Argentine (silvery thistle): Fantaisie Mazurka (Op. 21), piano (solo) (Oversize 8)
    - Ketterer, Eugene Flick et Flock: Galop du Ballet de Hertel, transcription pour piano, piano (solo) (signed "Jennie Butler, B. G. F. S." "Lizzie Cockrell, Fair Port, Northumberland Co., Virginia") (Oversize 8)
    - King, Robert A. Beyond the Gates of Paradise, words by Henry V. Neal, vocal (song) (medium voice) (Oversize 8)
    - Kleber, H. The Engagement Quadrille, piano (solos) (signed "Milly – (8)" "Jan. 10th 1885") (Oversize 9)
    - Kleber, H. Home Schottisch, arranged as a duet, piano (four hands) (Oversize 9)
    - Klengel, Julius Kindertrio No. 2 in G dur für Pianoforte, Violine u. Violoncell (Op. 25), piano trio (piano, violin, cello) (Oversize 9)
    - Klengel, Julius Kindertrio No. 3 in F dur für Pianoforte, Violine u. Violoncell (Op. 39), piano trio (piano, violin, cello) (Oversize 9)
    - Klengel, Julius Kindertrio No. 4 in D dur für Pianoforte, Violine u. Violoncell (Op. 39), piano trio (piano, violin, cello) (violin part) (Oversize 9)
    - Klengel, Julius Kindertrio No. 4 in D dur für Pianoforte, Violine u. Violoncell (Op. 39), piano trio (piano, violin, cello) (cello part) (Oversize 9)
    - Klickmann, F. Henri Sweet Hawaiian Moonlight (Tell Her of My Love), lyric by Harold G. Frost, vocal (solo or duet) (marked "Love") (Oversize 9)
    - Knauff, George P. Virginia Reels, Dedicated to Thomas Ritchie Esq. of Washington City, piano (solos) (signed "Phillie A. Stover" "Willow Grove" "Shenandoah County" "Virginia") (Oversize 9)
    - Koerner, Arthur Night and Love, words by Bulwer Lytton, vocal (song with piano accompaniment) (high voice) (Oversize 9)
    - Kohlmann, Clarence Love Light, words by E. A. Barrell, Jr., vocal (song) (Oversize 9)
    - Kohlmann, Clarence Royal King Divine, words by Elsie Duncan Yale, vocal (song) (tenor or soprano) (Oversize 9)
    - Kortlander, Max Tell Me, lyric by J. Will Callahan, vocal (song) (Oversize 9)
    - Kramer, A. Walter The Great Awakening, words by Gordon Johnstone, vocal (song with piano accompaniment) (signed by Winifred S. Myers) (Oversize 9)
    - Krug, D. The Best Piano Arrangement of Schubert's Serenade / Ständchen von F. Schubert, piano (solo) (Oversize 9)
    - Krug, D. Martha von F. V. Flotow (Op. 114), piano (solo) (signed "Milly A. Hinkley (9)" "March 28th 1885") (Oversize 9)
    - Krug, D. 3 Romantische Tonstücke in Liederform für Pianoforte No. 2: Abendlied (Op. 126), piano (solo) (Oversize 9)
    - Krug, D. Turkish Patrol Reveille, originally composed by Th. Michaelis, piano (solo) (Oversize 9)
    - Kurs, Adolphe Julia Waltz, arranged & affectionately dedicated to Miss Julia D. Hasbrouck (keyboard or harp solo) (signed by Phillie A Stover) (Oversize 9)
    - Kürsteiner, Jean Paul Deliverance (Op. 25), "Text from The Holy Writ, collaboration of Henrietta Falconer-Grant," vocal (song) (soprano or tenor) (marked "Ross") (Oversize 9)
    - Lachner Turandot Overture, (orchestral sheet music) (Oversize 9)
    - Lacome, P. Estudiantina, vocal (choral) (men's voices) (Oversize 9)
    - La Forge, Frank Two Songs with Piano Accompaniment: Come unto these yellow sands, vocal (song) (signed by Winifred S. Myers) (Oversize 9)
    - Lange, Arthur America Here's My Boy, words by Andrew B. Sterling, vocal (song) (Oversize 9)
    - Lange, Gustav Abenständchen (Evening Serenade) für pianoforte (Op. 224), piano (solo) (Oversize 9)
    - Lansing, G. L. Two Step: The Tale of a Seashell Introduction "Heidelberg Stein Song" from Pixley & Luders' Musical Comedy the Prince of Pilsen, banjo (duet) (signed by H. Leslie Conrad) (Oversize 9)
    - Lansing, G. L. Latest Gems for Mandolin and Guitar: The Darkies' Dream, (mandolin solo) (Oversize 9)
    - Lassen, Ed Evening, vocal (choral) (Oversize 9)
    - Lauder, Harry The Laddies Who Fought and Won, vocal (song) (Oversize 9)
    - Lauder, Harry I'm Going to Marry-arry, vocal (song) (Oversize 9)
    - Lauder, Harry We'll All Go Hame the Same Way, vocal (song) (Oversize 9)
    - Lauder, Harry There Is Somebody Waitin' for Me, vocal (song) (Oversize 9)
    - Laurendeau, L. P. Trolley-Galop, (orchestral sheet music) (includes sheet music for "Midway Plaisance" arr. by L. O. de Witt on the back) (Oversize 9)
    - Lecocq, Charles Gems of M'me Angot, comic opera, vocal (songs) (Oversize 9)
    - Lee, Alfred The Tichborne Trial and What Became of It, a Comic Vocal Medley, vocal (medley of songs) (Oversize 9)
    - Lee, Alfred The Flying Trapeze, written by George Leybourne, vocal (song) (Oversize 9)
    - Lee, Dorothy Out of the Dusk to You, words by Arthur J. Lamb, vocal (song) (Oversize 9)
    - Legnani, Louis Recueil des Mélodies moderns portages en quatre cahiers formant un grand pot-pourri pour la Guitarre seule, cahier I, guitar (solos) (signed by W. P. Graham) (Oversize 9)
    - Legnani, Louis Recueil des Mélodies moderns portages en quatre cahiers formant un grand pot-pourri pour la Guitarre seule, cahier II, guitar (solos) (signed by W. P. Graham) (Oversize 9)
    - Legnani, Louis Recueil des Mélodies moderns portages en quatre cahiers formant un grand pot-pourri pour la Guitarre seule, cahier III, guitar (solos) (signed by W. P. Graham) (Oversize 9)
    - Legnani, Louis Recueil des Mélodies moderns portages en quatre cahiers formant un grand pot-pourri pour la Guitarre seule, cahier IV, guitar (solos) (signed by W. P. Graham) (Oversize 9)
    - Legnani, Luigi Gran Pot-pourri con Introduzione e Coda per Chitarra sola sopra alcuni motive d'Opere Favorite (Op. 238), guitar (solo) (signed by W. P. Graham) (Oversize 9)
    - Legnani, Luigi Introduzione dell'Atto Qo. Nell'opera Ernani di Verdi ridotta per Chitarra sola, guitar (solo) (signed by W. P. Graham) (Oversize 9)
    - Legnani, Luigi Cavatina d'Elvira nell'Opera Ernani di Verdi ridatta per Chitarra sola, guitar (solo) (signed by W. P. Graham) (Oversize 9)
    - Lerman, J. W. Life Eternal, words by William J. Irons, vocal (song) (soprano or tenor) two copies (Oversize 9)
    - Levey, Harold Good-Bye, from Lady Billy, book and lyrics by Zelda Sears, vocal (song) (Oversize 9)
    - Levy, Sol P. Dramatic Tension No. 1, (marked as "The Man Is Dead") (orchestral sheet music) (Oversize 9)
    - Lewis, W. F. Andalusia: Valse Espanole, guitar (solo) (Oversize 9)
    - Leybach, J. The Palms (Les rameaux) (Op. 180), keyboard (solo) (Oversize 9)
    - Liddle, Samuel Abide with Me, words by Henry Francis Lyte, vocal (song) two copies (Oversize 9)
    - Liddle, Samuel How Lovely Are Thy Dwellings, vocal (song) two copies, both signed by Winifred S. Myers (Oversize 9)
    - Lincoln, Harry J. False Alarm, keyboard (solo) (Oversize 9)
    - Logan, Frederic Knight Pale Moon: an Indian Love Song, lyric by Jesse G. M. Glick, vocal (song with piano and Indian flute accompaniment) (Oversize 9)
    - Löhr, Hermann Songs in Exile, words by Arthur Stranger, vocal (song) (Oversize 9)
    - Loud, A. F. The Midnight Song, words by R. M. Offord, vocal (song) (Oversize 9)